You're also going to want some comfortable yoga type clothes.
Tank tops are great because sometimes the hoop can get a little bit slippery, so tank tops are awesome.
Definitely.
You need to clear a space.
Hooping takes a lot of room.
If you have stuff around you when you're hooping, there's a really good chance that you're going to break something.
Make sure that you clear a space and it's nice and comfortable with room for you to hoop around your waist, as well as taking it up and over your head.
The last thing we recommend, after you try a move, go ahead and put on your favorite song and rock out.
Music inspires fun and creativity.
Alright, let's do it.